now i know y'all not in my comments talking about empathy that can't be y'all that can't be y'all
no y'all not in my comments talking about we don't have to be like them you guys
it's we in your we y'all be acting like starting to be like them starts today
first of all charlie kirk don't believe in empathy he said it's a bad thing he said it's
new age made up shit he also said people got to be sacrificed in order to protect guns now if he
was saying that while fighting for reparations i may have a little bit of empathy but this white
on white violence he died damn b life comes at you fast let's see did he die someone in the comment
said he died they ain't say he dead yet listen he gone wow that's a tough break bro that's a tough
break what did he think was gonna happen when he got up there telling all these people secrets
what did he think was gonna happen that man said i'm gonna tell y'all honesty that was like the other
day that was like the other day but that man was on there i said this person was with epstein and that
person and i promise you i promise you hold on let me block this fool all of that was probably over
some capitalist bullshit like they didn't give him a job that he wanted or something that's it
so what are y'all talking about oh that was ben shapiro doing that damn i don't even to be very
honest they're all the same person to me ben shapiro candace owens charlie kirk they're all the
same person to me i don't well dang they're all the same person to me because at the end of the day
they all serve the same master why would you feel bad about it you know the thing about empathy
is that it requires energy it requires connectivity right and you know some people think empathy and
sympathy are the same thing and they're not the same thing so sympathy is the little performance
that y'all do on here where you feel bad because it looks good to you to feel bad that's sympathy it's a
it's a an act an act of acting you don't actually feel bad but it like looks good to feel bad in your
opinion so you feel bad that's sympathy empathy is when you are
literally feeling what the other person is feeling that's empathy when you put yourself in their shoes
i can't have empathy for someone like charlie kirk because i cannot be in his shoes i have no frame
of reference for that i have no cognizance for that there literally is nothing about his existence that
i can relate to so i don't have any empathy because i have no connectivity i have more connectivity
to someone who is a complete stranger that dies of a drug overdose than i do to someone like charlie
kirk because life is hard and i understand that because it takes very little for someone to end up
committing themselves to um an existence of numbness i understand that um you know some people think that
they are an elevated being for having compassion for those that have none and i don't see myself
or measure myself against that um i don't imagine my soul within the context of this this bullshit realm
at the end of the day there are people humans if you will who are incredibly harmful who want to see
you harmed and if that if having compassion for them makes you feel good well baby i'm not gonna stop you
but i i but i'll be damned if you're gonna be in my comments talking about have we lost all compassion
compassion no we have not we have not lost all compassion i have incredible compassion massive
amounts but not for this i'm not gonna tell y'all what i'm eating because they're not paying me to tell
you and i don't know you know i don't necessarily know i know where it's from and all you need to know
is that it ain't from israel okay am i gonna eat this whole bar this is my lunch 31 it's not from trader
joe's 31 that's crazy that man got murdered at 31 at a college event in the middle of a sentence
talking about black gangs what a way to go oh chanel he was actually taken out by an old white man
mm-hmm so in one of the whitest
whitery witty whites states in existence he didn't get murked in watts now they took him out in utah
they they said lady lady oleana i want you to know it was us ain't no way it was a black man that took
that man out not no not no utah right as that bullet hit him that man was in the middle of talking
shit about gangs white on white crime these thugs y'all these thugs let me see this shit
that man had a wife and two kids wanted people to be their best selves instead of being victim-minded
and spoke on a country having high morals and you have no empathy seem like you got no common sense
that's what it sounds like it seemed like you got no common sense now for the record i know that every
time i step out my house it could go down every time because that's what you that's how you live when
you when you're talking you know that every time you step out your house it could go down
so i want to tap in with y'all i told y'all the assassinations was gonna start
and um because we're in a time loop what y'all don't realize is that we're in the civil rights
movement again we're in the 60s again but we're in the mirror of it we're in the mirror of it
i'm sure there's somebody who know about space-time continuums and shit who could
say more to this so that's where we are i don't know what y'all having for dinner
i have some leftover chicken i have a uh um a chicken parmesan i'm gonna have that
what do i mean by the mirror of it well the civil rights movement of the 60s was happening in the
midst of the korean war which is essentially a proxy war and it was a fight for the ascertainment
of rights that were already promised here we are in 2025 we are in a proxy war with several places
and the white people are in a fight to ascertain rights that they already have the mirror so
the question will become oh and then and then we went into the vietnam war so the thing about a cycle
is that every time you go around it gets deeper that shooter was a paid shooter that was a sniper
knowledge comments that are valuable comments i'm not gonna acknowledge continuous nonsense
i'm not gonna acknowledge people who are coming in here saying charlie kirk is dead like that ain't
why we in here obviously we know charlie kirk is dead that's why we here and today on my show views
from amanda land we had an astrologist laura chung who was telling us about how the astrology of now
lines up with the same astrology of the revolutionary war so i hope everybody goes outside he's not in
critical condition he is dead charlie kirk has died after being shot at an event in utah president trump
says damn so i'm gonna go back to the work i was doing and uh make sure you go and check out this
today's episode of youth for a man lamb that was absolutely a sniper and um get your patchouli
not your patchouli get your pal santo get that protection spell going and don't let nobody try
and guilt you into having sympathy for the devil what about me and 19 keys by the way 19 keys is fine
as hell i don't know nothing else about 19 keys other than he's fine as hell just so we're clear
i don't know anything else so if y'all are like he's a misogynist blah blah i i don't i don't know
i don't know all i know is that he's fine that's all i'm saying i i just need to make that clear
because y'all like to be like well you i don't i don't know nothing else about that man but his but
his face is well is well constructed to my to my personal aesthetics and that's all i know
that's all i know so he has a fortunate face do i think they'll regulate guns they probably the one
that took him out so y'all like partner with him i literally say i don't know nothing about this man
other than he fine you talking about partner with him y'all are oh my god y'all are funny
bless your hearts bless bless your hearts okay um but uh yeah they got your boy up out of here boy
let me tell you let's say they get me up out of here
i want y'all to go on live and i want you to play so so death based all stars my boo
that's that's what i want the day that i leave this realm that's what i want i want everyone at 10 a.m
in and not at the same time because i want it to be like 10 a.m for the whole day okay
at 10 a.m because that's my favorite time 10 a.m i want y'all to play boy you should know that
i got you on my mind your secret admire that's what i would want somebody say you're blocked
and misspelled your j brand get the fuck out my live i've been watching you if your game is on
give me a call boo yes 10 a.m is my favorite time because the sun is like up but it's like
it's not still chilly it's like morning it's morning like we're in the morning we're hardcore
in it 10 a.m what do i think of the people who say they don't condone political violence
i think they full of shit and i think they don't understand that violence
is always political yeah yeah violence is always political
like what are we like you know so when people say that it's just well here's the thing that i also
say people a lot of people think that they sound real smart and i can tell you i know they not because
i used to sound like them and from where i am now looking back i'm like oh you you was not
you was not smart girl oh like when people say like political strategy i'm looking at them crazy
i'm looking at them crazy when people start talking about political strategy i'm just like baby
you're not there yet you're not there yet i think you might get there i think i think you might get
there but you're not there yet if if you're talking about political strategy you're not there yet
no um yes i did paint this behind me um because the the strategy really needs to be apolitical
yeah so if you're talking about political strategy you're already you're behind
but you'll catch up if you want to you'll catch up if you want to um anywho not much else to say
unless you got a question i don't got much else to say smoking a cigarette and not a joint is crazy
is it really that crazy is it really like crazy that she would be smoking a newport
in the bronx because that's what she's doing smoking a newport in the bronx is is that really crazy
i hate this internet y'all say such wild corny shit and if i was if you were in front of my face you
wouldn't say it because you know i'd be like you sound corny as hell um someone compared charlie
kirk's assassination to martin luther king jr's assassination the internet don't hate me
no no the internet don't hate me but i i know that sounded hot when you said it it sounded like
some shit to say you was like oh i'm about to but it don't hate me so you know there's that
um anywho my lipstick i added ate up all my lipstick will this activate more of the white
nationalists i don't know i don't think about the white nationalists he was absolutely okay with
children being shot in school absolutely literally said they should be sacrificed uh-huh
political violence is horrible are you an op where where do y'all come with these lines it's like you
hear someone say it and you'd be like yeah that's some hot shit to say political violence is horrible
i don't know if y'all have i just i don't know it's hard for me to relate to like such a
it's hard for me to relate to such a dis um what's what i'm looking for to such a non-realistic
claudia i was gonna send it to you when people say political violence is horrible i'm just like
what what what what planet have you been on what planet have you been on also like political violence
he was a right-wing commentator dissonance was the word thank you because you saw me reaching
it's like where is it where is it dissonance was the word dissonance i'm like where learn something
about belfast northern ireland then tell me about political violence learn something about tulsa oklahoma
then tell me about political violence learn something about the rabbit proof fence
in australia then tell me about political violence
learn something about the 38th parallel in korea about the the massacre at jeju island and then tell
me about political violence you know i don't know you think charlie kirk being assassinated is
political violence i have some examples of political violence here in the comments rosewood
oscarville he was going on in nepal in indonesia do y'all remember kent state niggas get shot every
day b dairy the chicago fire palestine killing black folks who just tried to vote this is political
violence flint michigan the chicago riots jim crow and lynching this is political violence
the public of congo the okoe massacre this is political violence the move bombing in philadelphia
the top supermarket in buffalo this is political violence the congo katrina
the assassination of all of our leaders gerrymandering in texas
all of this is political violence all of this is political violence and you want to tell me about
charlie kirk baby no you know they say that it's best to go doing what you love
and he left doing what he loved spreading disinformation to white people
grounded in racism and bigotry backed up by an inflated ego funded by the world's worst people
so you know he went the way many would wish to go living his dream y'all have a great evening
peace be unto you and may the force be with you